We'll see it tomorrow, it's Daniel Sancho's trial.
la vemos mañana es el juicio de Daniel
Yes, well, surely by the time
Sancho Sí bueno seguramente para cuando
people are seeing this extract,
la gente esté viendo este extracto
eh, that hearing that
eh Ya habrá tenido lugar esa vista que
Daniel has today, Monday, will have already taken place
tiene Daniel hoy lunes
with the judge. Okay, you know, let's see,
con con el juez vale Ya sabéis que a ver
I don't rule out the possibility of it being suspended again,
yo no descarto que se vuelva a suspender
eh, because they were saying that it was
eh porque estaban diciendo que era
complicated, that it was
complicado que era
complicated, one thing that they have to
complicado una cosa que tienen que
comply with is an interpreter, HM, it's an
cumplir es un intérprete HM es un
interpreter from Thai to Spanish who
intérprete del tailandés al español que
knows how to handle themselves in legal terms,
se sepa manejar en términos jurídicos
okay, the other time they put it to him by
vale la otra vez se lo pusieron por
video call and Daniel demanded that no, that he
videollamada y Daniel exigió que no que
has the right to have it present and that's how it's
tiene derecho a tenerlo presente y así
going to be, it's true, José Luis, very good
va a ser es verdad José Luis muy buena
memory. Tomorrow the kids there's also
memoria mañana la chavalería también hay
another trial, that of Ali with the ex.
otro juicio que es el de Ali con el ex
Well, this is what has come out. An
Bueno pues esto es lo que ha salido una
inmate says that Daniel Sancho is an
reclusa cuenta que Daniel Sancho es un
idol in prison, people talk a lot
ídolo en la cárcel la gente habla mucho
about him, so maybe and with everything, the guy
de él o sea que capaz y con todo el tío
is there as if he were an
esté allí como si fuera un
influencer, okay, a female inmate
influencer vale una mujer interna en
has commented on a lot of things and now they are
cosa mui ha comentado en y ahora son
talking about the attitudes that the
soles las actitudes que manifiesta el
confessed murderer of Edwin Arrieta shows, he is
asesino confeso de Edwin Arrieta es
strong, decent, and friendly, Dano is very
fuerte decente y amigable dano está mu
close to the sentence he faces
cerca de la pena a la que se enfrenta
after  murder and dismember the
tras asesinar y descuartizar al cirujano
Colombian surgeon Edwin Arrieta there are only
colombiano Edwin Arrieta tan solo queda
72 hours left until the light comes out well
72 horas para que salga la luz la bueno
by the time you're watching this video it will have already been
para cuando estéis viendo Este vídeo ya
okay this news I think
habrá sido vale es que esta noticia creo
is from yesterday or the day before
que es de ayer o antes de
yesterday by the time you're watching this
ayer para cuando estéis viendo Este
video most of you will surely have already
vídeo La mayoría seguramente ya habrá
happened whatever it is I don't rule out what I've
sucedido lo que sea yo no descarto lo
told you eh I don't rule out that it will be
que os he dicho eh yo no descarto que se
suspended again because it is
vuelva a suspender porque es que es
mandatory that they do the interpreter
obligatorio que hagan lo del intérprete
and they say that
y dicen que es
the prison sentence or
complicado la pena de prisión o la
death is complicated as contemplated by
muerte tal y como contempla la
Thai legislation in this type of
legislación tailandesa en este tipo de
events eh The move is that if he
sucesos eh La Movida es que si él
admits to the facts there is no more trial they
reconoce los hechos no hay más juicio le
reduce the sentence and I think he remains
rebajan la pena y creo que se queda
on
en
permanent life imprisonment no
permanente perpetua no
eh and then he can get it
eh y ya luego puede ir consiguiendo con
reduced with his behavior okay I
el comportamiento reducirlo vale me
imagine the team and now they are soles
imagino el equipo de y ahora son soles
that has been installed in the Asian country
que lleva instalado en el país asiático
since the cook's confession came to light
desde que saliese a la luz la confesión
has chatted with a prisoner
del cocinero ha charlado con una presa
who is in the same
que se encuentra en la misma
prison How how the journalists have
prisión Cómo cómo los periodistas han
chatted with a prisoner who is
charlado con una presa que está
interned with him
internada con él
how she recognizes  that people talk
cómo ella reconoce que la gente habla
a lot about him because they know that he is the son
mucho de él porque saben que es el hijo
of a famous Spanish actor. I think he is
de un reconocido actor español Me parece
very handsome and elegant. He is a strong man,
muy guapo y elegante es un hombre fuerte
a decent man, and he is also friendly.
un hombre decente además es amigable
Well, a decent man tells you,
Bueno un hombre decente te dice
eh, ofu. I'm noticing that I'm going to get
eh ofu Me estoy notando que me voy a
sick,
poner malito
family. A kiss, Rebeca, sweetheart. Thank you very much
familia Un beso Rebeca corazón Muchas
for renewing that I'm going to get
gracias por renovar que me voy a poner
sick,
malito
family, that I'm going to get
familia que me voy a poner
sick. However, she has never had any contact with him because of a law that prevents men and women from maintaining contact inside the prison. She says that she found out about him thanks to an inmate who sent her a snack with a hidden message in a wrapper. She wanted to meet Daniel because he was on television and his
porque él salió en televisión y su
news was very famous. So she wanted to
noticia era muy famosa Así que quería
meet him and greet him, but there is only one
conocerlo y saludarlo pero solo hay una
way to send messages with them,
manera de enviarnos mensajes con ellos
sending a message with a snack and if he receives
enviando mensaje con snack y Si recibe
the message, he can also eat. He
el mensaje también puede comer él nos
told us that he was doing well. The aforementioned
dijo que se encontraba va bien el citado
program has also revealed that the
programa también ha revelado que el
prisoner shares Zelda with 10 other prisoners,
Preso comparte Zelda con otros 10 presos
sports, yoga, and reading are
el deporte el yoga y la lectura forman
part of his
parte de su rutina
daily routine, this is what he has left, what he has
diaria es lo que le queda en lo que le
left. But well, I mean, not very friendly,
queda Pero bueno o sea muy amigable no
but well, very friendly and a man
pero bueno muy amigable y un hombre
decent mother of God what you have to hear what you have to
decente madre de Dios lo que hay que oír
hear no
lo que hay que oír no